<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<odoo>
    <data>
        <template id="insurance_waiver_template">
            <t t-call="report.html_container">
				<t t-foreach="docs" t-as="o">
					<div class="page" style="font-family:Arial;">
                        <div class="text-center">
                            <h3><b>WAIVER WITH SPECIAL POWER OF ATTORNEY</b></h3><br/>
                        </div>
                        <div class="text-justify">
                            <p style="font-size:16px;">
                                I, &#160;<b><t t-esc="str(o.get_approvers_name(o.id)).upper()"/></b>&#160;, of legal age, Filipino, &#160;<b><t t-esc="o.marital"/></b>&#160; and a resident of
                                <t t-if="o.barangay_id and o.complete_add">
                                    &#160;<b><t class="text-uppercase" t-esc="o.complete_add"/>,  <t t-esc="o.barangay_id.display_name"/></b>&#160;
                                </t>
                                <t t-if="o.barangay_id and not o.complete_add">
                                    &#160;<b><t class="text-uppercase" t-esc="o.barangay_id.display_name"/></b>&#160;
                                </t>
                                <t t-if="not o.barangay_id and not o.complete_add and o.municipality_id">
                                   &#160; <b><t class="text-uppercase" t-esc="employee_id.municipality_id.display_name"/></b>&#160;
                                </t>
                                <t t-if="not o.barangay_id and not o.complete_add and not o.municipality_id and o.province_id">
                                    &#160;<b><t class="text-uppercase" t-esc="employee_id.province_id.display_name"/></b>&#160;
                                </t>
                                <t t-if="not o.barangay_id and not o.complete_add and not o.municipality_id and not o.province_id and o.region_id">
                                    &#160;<b><t class="text-uppercase" t-esc="employee_id.region_id.display_name"/></b>&#160;
                                </t>, Philippines hereunder undertake and declare the following, to wit:
                            </p>
                            <p style="font-size:16px;">
                                That I am fully aware that my employer, the &#160;<b><t t-esc="o.company_id.name"/></b>&#160;&#160; hereinafter referred
                                to as <b>EMPLOYER</b>, intends to procure a Group Life Insurance package from both Sun Life Financial
                                and Philam Life Insurance companies for participating employees of &#160;<b>EMPLOYER</b>, with the consent
                                of employees and without any expense on their part;<br/><br/>
                                That by signing this document, I have fully agreed and consented to the terms and conditions of &#160;<b> EMPLOYER</b> as
                                to the disposition of the proceeds of the above-mentioned insurance policies if anything happens
                                to undersigned during the effectivity of both insurance policies;<br/><br/>
                                That I accept and agree to the sharing scheme of the insurance proceeds of said insurance policies, to wit:
                            </p>
                        </div>
                        <table style="font-size:16px;width:100%;border-collapse: collapse;">
                            <tr>
                                <td style="width:2%;padding:4px;text-align:left;vertical-align:center;">
                                </td>
                                <td style="width:3%;padding:4px;text-align:left;vertical-align:center;">
                                    <p style="font-size:16px;"><b>a.</b></p>
                                </td>
                                <td style="width:95%;padding:4px;text-align:justify;vertical-align:center;">
                                    <p style="font-size:16px;">
                                        For hospitalization refunds due to accidents: ten percent (10%) of the full amount
                                        reimbursed by the insurance company shall be retained by <b>EMPLOYER</b> as service
                                        fee, and the balance shall be turned-over to the undersigned; and
                                    </p>
                                </td>
                            </tr>
                            <tr>
                                <td style="width:2%;padding:4px;text-align:left;vertical-align:center;">
                                </td>
                                <td style="width:3%;padding:4px;text-align:left;vertical-align:center;">
                                    <p style="font-size:16px;"><b>b.</b></p>
                                </td>
                                <td style="width:95%;padding:4px;text-align:justify;vertical-align:center;">
                                    <p style="font-size:16px;">
                                        For death, either natural or by accident: fifty percent (50%) of the full insurance
                                        proceeds shall go to my heirs and survivors, and fifty percent (50%) will be retained by
                                        <b>EMPLOYER</b> as service fee and compensation for the sudden loss of a valued employee.
                                    </p>
                                </td>
                            </tr>
                        </table>
                        <div class="text-justify">
                            <p style="font-size:16px;">
                                I fully understand, accept and agree that the ten percent (10%) deduction is a necessary
                                expense for the processing, follow-ups and miscellaneous expenses to claim the insurance
                                proceeds of the life insurance, and that the fifty percent (50%) share of <b>EMPLOYER</b> in the
                                insurance proceeds is both a necessary expense in processing the insurance claims and an
                                indemnification to <b>EMPLOYER</b> for the ensuing operational difficulties, opportunity losses,
                                expenses and losses in finding a replacement due to the untimely death of an employee;<br/><br/>

                                I further fully understand and accept the full prerogative of &#160;<b> EMPLOYER </b>&#160; to pool the amounts
                                generated from insurance proceeds mentioned above either in a trust fund or a special
                                account to be used as payments for future insurance premiums of the abovementioned insurance
                                policies or any insurance policies for their employees and for other employee benefits as
                                may be adopted by <b>EMPLOYER</b> in the future;<br/><br/>

                                NOW THEREFORE, premises considered, I hereby waive, in favor of &#160;<b> EMPLOYER </b>&#160;, ten percent (10%) of
                                the insurance proceeds reimbursable by The Manufacturer's Life Insurance Company, Inc. and Philam Life Insurance
                                companies in case I am hospitalized due to an accident, and I further waive fifty percent
                                (50%) of the life insurance proceeds from both insurance companies mentioned above in case
                                the undersigned dies either through natural cause or through accident.<br/><br/>

                                Furthermore, I hereby constitiute the President of the Company, or any duly authorized representative
                                of <b>EMPLOYER</b>, as my Attorney-in-Fact with full authority to transact with Sun Life Financial and Philam
                                Life in the processing of all claims and to automatically deduct the amounts representing the
                                above-mentioned percentages due to <b>EMPLOYER</b> from the insurance proceeds granted by both insurance
                                companies.<br/><br/>

                                <b>I HAVE SATISFIED MYSELF FULLY AS TO THE NATURE OF THE OBLIGATIONS CONTAINED HEREIN AND HAVE
                                    SIGNED THIS WAIVER AND GRANT OF SPECIAL POWER  &#160;OF ATTORNEY VOLUNTARILY.</b><br/>
                            </p>
                        </div><br/><br/>
                        <div class="text-center">
                            <b><p style="font-size:18px;text-align:center;" class="text-uppercase" t-esc="str(o.get_approvers_name(o.id)).upper()"/></b>
                            <p>_______________________________________</p>
                            <p style="font-size:16px;">NAME OF EMPLOYEE</p><br/>
                            <p style="font-size:18px;"><b>Witnesses:</b></p>
                        </div>
                        <div class="row">
                            <div class="col-xs-6 text-center">
                                <span>_______________________________________</span>
                            </div>
                            <div class="col-xs-6 text-center">
                                <span>_______________________________________</span>
                            </div>
                        </div><br/><br/><br/><br/><br/><br/>
                        <div class="text-left">
                            <span>____________________________</span><br/>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                </t>
            </t>
        </template>
    </data>
</odoo>
