<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<odoo>
    <data>
        <!--NON Disclosure Agreement-->
        <template id="report_non_disclosure_template">
			<t t-call="report.html_container">
				<t t-foreach="docs" t-as="o">
					<div class="page" style="font-family:Arial;">
                        <br/>
                        <div class="text-right">
                            <p style="font-weight:bold;font-size:16px;"> HR Form 123</p>
                        </div>
                        <div class="text-center">
                            <h2><b>EMPLOYEE NON-DISCLOSURE AGREEMENT</b></h2><br/><br/>
                        </div>
                        <!--<div class="text-left">-->
                        <div class="text-justify">
                            <p style="font-size:18px;">This Employee Non-Disclosure Agreement is entered into between &#160;<b><t class="text-uppercase" t-esc="str(o.get_approvers_name(employee_id.id)).upper()"/></b>&#160;
                                (“Employee”) and &#160;<b><t class="text-uppercase" t-esc="company_id.name"/></b>&#160; (“Employer”).</p>
                        </div>
                        <!--</div>-->
                        <div class="text-center">
                            <p style="font-size:20px;"><b>RECITALS:</b></p>
                        </div>
                        <table style="font-size:18px;width:100%;border-collapse: collapse;">
                            <tr>
                                <td style="width:2%;padding:4px;text-align:center;vertical-align:center;">

                                </td>
                                <td style="width:3%;padding:4px;text-align:left;vertical-align:center;">
                                    <p style="font-size:18px;"><b>A.</b></p>
                                </td>
                                <td style="width:95%;padding:4px;text-align:justify;vertical-align:center;">
                                    <p style="font-size:18px;">The success of an <b>EMPLOYER’S</b> business depends on <b>EMPLOYER'S</b> possession of confidential,
                                    proprietary information, not generally known to others, including specialized information about research, development,
                                    production, marketing, and management.</p>
                                </td>
                            </tr>
                            <tr>
                                <td style="width:2%;padding:4px;text-align:center;vertical-align:center;">

                                </td>
                                <td style="width:3%;padding:4px;text-align:left;vertical-align:center;">
                                    <p style="font-size:18px;"><b>B.</b></p>
                                </td>
                                <td style="width:95%;padding:4px;text-align:justify;vertical-align:center;">
                                    <p style="font-size:18px;"><b>EMPLOYER</b> wishes to protect its confidential proprietary
                                        information and ensure that all employees agree to maintain the confidentiality of this information.</p>
                                </td>
                            </tr>
                            <tr>
                                <td style="width:2%;padding:4px;text-align:center;vertical-align:center;">

                                </td>
                                <td style="width:3%;padding:4px;text-align:left;vertical-align:center;">
                                    <p style="font-size:18px;"><b>C.</b></p>
                                </td>
                                <td style="width:95%;padding:4px;text-align:justify;vertical-align:center;">
                                    <p style="font-size:18px;">Employee acknowledges that <b>EMPLOYER</b> desires to protect its confidential
                                        proprietary information, that his/her employment creates a duty of trust and confidentiality
                                        to <b>EMPLOYER</b> with respect to its confidential proprietary information and, as a condition of employment
                                        or continued employment with <b>EMPLOYER</b>, <b>EMPLOYEE</b>  agrees to be bound by the terms of this Agreement.</p>
                                </td>
                            </tr>
                        </table>
                        <div class="text-center">
                            <p style="font-size:20px;"><b>AGREEMENT:</b></p>
                        </div>
                        <div class="text-justify">
                            <p style="font-size:18px;">WHEREFORE, <b>EMPLOYER</b> and <b>EMPLOYEE</b> agree as follows:</p>
                        </div>
                        <div class="text-center">
                            <p style="font-size:20px;"><b>ARTICLE I: CONFIDENTIAL INFORMATION</b></p>
                        </div>
                        <table style="font-size:18px;width:100%;border-collapse: collapse;">
                            <tr>
                                <td style="width:2%;padding:4px;text-align:center;vertical-align:center;">

                                </td>
                                <td style="width:3%;padding:4px;text-align:center;vertical-align:center;">

                                </td>
                                <td style="width:3%;padding:4px;text-align:left;vertical-align:center;">
                                    <p style="font-size:18px;"><b>1.1</b></p>
                                </td>
                                <td style="width:92%;padding:4px;text-align:justify;vertical-align:center;">
                                    <p style="font-size:18px;">The terms "Confidential Information" and "Proprietary Data"
                                        mean information and data not generally known outside the company concerning
                                        Employer or its businesses and the Employer's business and technical information,
                                        including but not limited to, patent applications, information relating to inventions,
                                        discoveries, products, plans, calculations, concepts, design sheets, design data,
                                        system design, blueprints, computer programs, algorithms, software, firmware, hardware,
                                        manuals, drawings, photographs, devices, samples, models, processes, specifications,
                                        instructions, research, test procedures and results, equipment, identity and description
                                        of computerized records, customer lists, supplier identity, marketing and sales plans,
                                        financial information, business plans, costs, pricing information, and all other
                                        concepts or ideas involving or reasonably related to the business or prospective business
                                        of Employer, or information received by the Employer as to which there is a bona fide obligation,
                                        contractual or otherwise, on Employer's part, not to disclose same.</p>
                                </td>
                            </tr>
                            <tr>
                                <td style="width:2%;padding:4px;text-align:center;vertical-align:center;">

                                </td>
                                <td style="width:3%;padding:4px;text-align:center;vertical-align:center;">

                                </td>
                                <td style="width:3%;padding:4px;text-align:left;vertical-align:center;">
                                    <p style="font-size:18px;"><b>1.2</b></p>
                                </td>
                                <td style="width:92%;padding:4px;text-align:justify;vertical-align:center;">
                                    <p style="font-size:18px;"><b>EMPLOYEE</b> understands and agrees that the Confidential
                                        Information and Proprietary Data constitute trade secrets of <b>EMPLOYER</b> and that
                                        at all times material to this Agreement, Employer has taken all reasonable steps
                                        to protect the confidentiality of this information.</p>
                                </td>
                            </tr>
                            <tr>
                                <td style="width:2%;padding:4px;text-align:center;vertical-align:center;">

                                </td>
                                <td style="width:3%;padding:4px;text-align:center;vertical-align:center;">

                                </td>
                                <td style="width:3%;padding:4px;text-align:left;vertical-align:center;">
                                    <p style="font-size:18px;"><b>1.3</b></p>
                                </td>
                                <td style="width:92%;padding:4px;text-align:justify;vertical-align:center;">
                                    <p style="font-size:18px;"><b>EMPLOYEE</b> agrees not to use Confidential Information
                                        and/or Proprietary Data for the benefit of any other person, corporation or entity,
                                        other than the <b>EMPLOYER</b>, during the term of <b>EMPLOYEE'S</b> employment with <b>EMPLOYER</b>, or any time thereafter.</p>
                                </td>
                            </tr>
                            <tr>
                                <td style="width:2%;padding:4px;text-align:center;vertical-align:center;">

                                </td>
                                <td style="width:3%;padding:4px;text-align:center;vertical-align:center;">

                                </td>
                                <td style="width:3%;padding:4px;text-align:left;vertical-align:center;">
                                    <p style="font-size:18px;"><b>1.4</b></p>
                                </td>
                                <td style="width:92%;padding:4px;text-align:justify;vertical-align:center;">
                                    <p style="font-size:18px;"><b>EMPLOYEE</b> agrees that the Confidential Information and Proprietary
                                        Data shall be and remain the exclusive property of <b>EMPLOYER</b> and shall not be removed 
                                        from the premises of <b>EMPLOYER</b> under any circumstances whatsoever without the prior 
                                        written consent of <b>EMPLOYER</b>, and if removed, shall be immediately returned to <b>EMPLOYER</b> 
                                        upon any termination of <b>EMPLOYEE'S</b> employment, and no copies thereof may be kept by EMPLOYEE.</p>
                                </td>
                            </tr>
                            <tr>
                                <td style="width:2%;padding:4px;text-align:center;vertical-align:center;">

                                </td>
                                <td style="width:3%;padding:4px;text-align:center;vertical-align:center;">

                                </td>
                                <td style="width:3%;padding:4px;text-align:left;vertical-align:center;">
                                    <p style="font-size:18px;"><b>1.5</b></p>
                                </td>
                                <td style="width:92%;padding:4px;text-align:justify;vertical-align:center;">
                                    <p style="font-size:18px;">All notes, notebooks, memorandums, computer disks and other similar
                                        repositories of information containing or relating in any way to Confidential Information
                                        and/or Proprietary Data shall be the property of <b>EMPLOYER</b>. All such items made or compiled
                                        by <b>EMPLOYEE</b> or made available to <b>EMPLOYEE</b> during the period of employment, including all
                                        copies thereof, shall be held by <b>EMPLOYEE</b> in trust and solely for the benefit of <b>EMPLOYER</b>
                                        and shall be delivered to the <b>EMPLOYER</b> by <b>EMPLOYEE</b> upon termination of employment with <b>EMPLOYER</b>,
                                        or at any other time upon the request of the <b>EMPLOYER</b>.</p>
                                </td>
                            </tr>
                            <tr>
                                <td style="width:2%;padding:4px;text-align:center;vertical-align:center;">

                                </td>
                                <td style="width:3%;padding:4px;text-align:center;vertical-align:center;">

                                </td>
                                <td style="width:3%;padding:4px;text-align:left;vertical-align:center;">
                                    <p style="font-size:18px;"><b>1.6</b></p>
                                </td>
                                <td style="width:92%;padding:4px;text-align:justify;vertical-align:center;">
                                    <p style="font-size:18px;"><b>EMPLOYEE</b> agrees that Employee shall not disclose to any other person 
                                        or entity, either directly or indirectly, the Confidential Information and/or Proprietary Data. 
                                        <b>EMPLOYEE</b> understands that the use or disclosure of any of the Confidential Information and/or
                                        Proprietary Data may be cause for an action at law or in equity in an appropriate court and 
                                        that without waiving the right to collect damages from <b>EMPLOYEE</b>, <b>EMPLOYER</b> shall be entitled
                                        to an injunction prohibiting the use or disclosure of the Confidential Information and 
                                        Proprietary Data.</p>
                                </td>
                            </tr>
                        </table>
                        <div class="text-center">
                            <p style="font-size:20px;"><b>ARTICLE II: INVENTIONS</b></p>
                        </div>
                        <table style="font-size:18px;width:100%;border-collapse: collapse;">
                            <tr>
                                <td style="width:2%;padding:4px;text-align:center;vertical-align:center;">

                                </td>
                                <td style="width:3%;padding:4px;text-align:center;vertical-align:center;">

                                </td>
                                <td style="width:3%;padding:4px;text-align:left;vertical-align:center;">
                                    <p style="font-size:18px;"><b>2.1</b></p>
                                </td>
                                <td style="width:92%;padding:4px;text-align:justify;vertical-align:center;">
                                    <p style="font-size:18px;"><b>EMPLOYEE</b> shall promptly disclose to <b>EMPLOYER</b>, in writing,
                                        all inventions, ideas, discoveries, and improvements whether or not patentable or
                                        registrable under Copyright or similar statutes, made or conceived or reduced to practice
                                        or learned by <b>EMPLOYEE</b>, either alone or jointly with others, during the period of
                                        employment with <b>EMPLOYER</b>.  <b>EMPLOYEE</b> agrees that all such inventions (intellectual,
                                        visual or material) are the sole property of Employer.</p>
                                </td>
                            </tr>
                            <tr>
                                <td style="width:2%;padding:4px;text-align:center;vertical-align:center;">

                                </td>
                                <td style="width:3%;padding:4px;text-align:center;vertical-align:center;">

                                </td>
                                <td style="width:3%;padding:4px;text-align:left;vertical-align:center;">
                                    <p style="font-size:18px;"><b>2.2</b></p>
                                </td>
                                <td style="width:92%;padding:4px;text-align:justify;vertical-align:center;">
                                    <p style="font-size:18px;"><b>EMPLOYEE</b> assigns to <b>EMPLOYER</b> all right, title and
                                        interest in and to any and all inventions, ideas, discoveries, and improvements,
                                        with the exception of inventions, ideas, discoveries, and improvements that qualify
                                        for protection under Section 2.3. below.</p>
                                </td>
                            </tr>
                            <tr>
                                <td style="width:2%;padding:4px;text-align:center;vertical-align:center;">

                                </td>
                                <td style="width:3%;padding:4px;text-align:center;vertical-align:center;">

                                </td>
                                <td style="width:3%;padding:4px;text-align:left;vertical-align:center;">
                                    <p style="font-size:18px;"><b>2.3</b></p>
                                </td>
                                <td style="width:92%;padding:4px;text-align:justify;vertical-align:center;">
                                    <p style="font-size:18px;">This Agreement does not require assignment of an
                                        invention that is fully qualified for protection under relevant state labor code(s),
                                        which may provide as follows:<br/>
                                        Any provision in an employment agreement which provides that an <b>EMPLOYEE</b> shall assign
                                        or offer to assign any of his or her rights in an invention to his or her EMPLOYER
                                        shall not apply to an invention for which no equipment, supplies, facility or trade
                                        secret information of the <b>EMPLOYER</b> was used and which was developed entirely on the
                                        <b>EMPLOYEE’S</b> time, and (a) which does not relate (1) to the business of the employer
                                        or (2) to the employer’s actual or demonstrably anticipated research or development,
                                        or (b) which does not result from any work performed by the employee for the employer.</p>
                                </td>
                            </tr>
                        </table>
                        <div class="text-center">
                            <p style="font-size:20px;"><b>ARTICLE III: COVENANT NOT TO COMPETE</b></p>
                        </div>
                        <table style="font-size:18px;width:100%;border-collapse: collapse;">
                            <tr>
                                <td style="width:2%;padding:4px;text-align:center;vertical-align:center;">

                                </td>
                                <td style="width:3%;padding:4px;text-align:center;vertical-align:center;">

                                </td>
                                <td style="width:3%;padding:4px;text-align:left;vertical-align:center;">
                                    <p style="font-size:18px;"><b>3.1</b></p>
                                </td>
                                <td style="width:92%;padding:4px;text-align:justify;vertical-align:center;">
                                    <p style="font-size:18px;">During <b>EMPLOYEE’S</b>  employment with <b>EMPLOYER</b>, 
                                        <b>EMPLOYEE</b> agrees not to engage in any business competitive with any business of
                                        <b>EMPLOYER</b> without <b>EMPLOYER'S</b> prior written consent.</p>
                                </td>
                            </tr>
                            <tr>
                                <td style="width:2%;padding:4px;text-align:center;vertical-align:center;">

                                </td>
                                <td style="width:3%;padding:4px;text-align:center;vertical-align:center;">

                                </td>
                                <td style="width:3%;padding:4px;text-align:left;vertical-align:center;">
                                    <p style="font-size:18px;"><b>3.2</b></p>
                                </td>
                                <td style="width:92%;padding:4px;text-align:justify;vertical-align:center;">
                                    <p style="font-size:18px;">After termination of employment with <b>EMPLOYER</b>, 
                                        <b>EMPLOYEE</b> agrees that if he/she engages in employment or other activities independently
                                        or in association with others in any business competitive with any business of
                                        <b>EMPLOYER</b> or any business which may reasonably be expected to compete with any business
                                        of <b>EMPLOYER</b>, <b>EMPLOYEE</b> is required to inform the prospective <b>EMPLOYER</b> or association
                                        that <b>EMPLOYEE</b> cannot divulge any secrets or Confidential or Proprietary Information
                                        that <b>EMPLOYEE</b> may have learned during <b>EMPLOYEE’S</b>  employment with <b>EMPLOYER</b>.  "In association
                                        with others" shall include accepting any employment with, or rendering, directly or
                                        indirectly, advice or assistance of any kind to any person, partnership, corporation,
                                        association, or other organization.</p>
                                </td>
                            </tr>
                            <tr>
                                <td style="width:2%;padding:4px;text-align:center;vertical-align:center;">

                                </td>
                                <td style="width:3%;padding:4px;text-align:center;vertical-align:center;">

                                </td>
                                <td style="width:3%;padding:4px;text-align:left;vertical-align:center;">
                                    <p style="font-size:18px;"><b>3.3</b></p>
                                </td>
                                <td style="width:92%;padding:4px;text-align:justify;vertical-align:center;">
                                    <p style="font-size:18px;">On signing this contract, the <b>EMPLOYEE</b> agrees that
                                        during the course of  employment and immediately following the termination of
                                        the relationship with the <b>EMPLOYER</b> for any reason, whether with or without good
                                        cause or for any or no cause, at the option either of the <b>EMPLOYER</b> or the <b>EMPLOYEE</b>,
                                        with or without notice, the <b>EMPLOYEE</b> will NOT, without the prior written consent of
                                        the <b>EMPLOYER</b>, a) serve as a partner, employee, consultant, officer, director, manager,
                                        agent, associate, investor, or otherwise. or b) directly or indirectly, own, purchase,
                                        organize or take preparatory steps for the organization of, or c) build, design, finance,
                                        acquire, lease, operate, manage, invest in, work or consult for or otherwise affiliate
                                        with, any business in competition with or otherwise similar to the <b>EMPLOYER</b>’s business
                                        within the <b>EMPLOYER</b>’s area of operation for a period of five (5) years, nor shall the
                                        <b>EMPLOYEE’S</b>   relatives up to the third civil degree of consanguinity be involved in any
                                        business that directly competes with the <b>EMPLOYER</b>’s business.</p>
                                </td>
                            </tr>
                        </table>
                        <div class="text-center">
                            <p style="font-size:20px;"><b>ARTICLE IV: MISCELLANEOUS PROVISIONS</b></p>
                        </div>
                        <table style="font-size:18px;width:100%;border-collapse: collapse;">
                            <tr>
                                <td style="width:2%;padding:4px;text-align:center;vertical-align:center;">

                                </td>
                                <td style="width:3%;padding:4px;text-align:center;vertical-align:center;">

                                </td>
                                <td style="width:3%;padding:4px;text-align:left;vertical-align:center;">
                                    <p style="font-size:18px;"><b>4.1</b></p>
                                </td>
                                <td style="width:92%;padding:4px;text-align:justify;vertical-align:center;">
                                    <p style="font-size:18px;">All provisions of this Agreement shall be severable for purposes of enforcement.
                                        If any provision or clause of this Agreement is unenforceable at law or in equity,
                                        such clause or provision shall be severed from the remainder of this Agreement, and
                                        the remainder of this Agreement shall continue to be enforceable, according to its terms.</p>
                                </td>
                            </tr>
                            <tr>
                                <td style="width:2%;padding:4px;text-align:center;vertical-align:center;">

                                </td>
                                <td style="width:3%;padding:4px;text-align:center;vertical-align:center;">

                                </td>
                                <td style="width:3%;padding:4px;text-align:left;vertical-align:center;">
                                    <p style="font-size:18px;"><b>4.2</b></p>
                                </td>
                                <td style="width:92%;padding:4px;text-align:justify;vertical-align:center;">
                                    <p style="font-size:18px;">This Agreement shall be interpreted under and governed by the
                                        laws of the Republic of the Philippines.</p>
                                </td>
                            </tr>
                            <tr>
                                <td style="width:2%;padding:4px;text-align:center;vertical-align:center;">

                                </td>
                                <td style="width:3%;padding:4px;text-align:center;vertical-align:center;">

                                </td>
                                <td style="width:3%;padding:4px;text-align:left;vertical-align:center;">
                                    <p style="font-size:18px;"><b>4.3</b></p>
                                </td>
                                <td style="width:92%;padding:4px;text-align:justify;vertical-align:center;">
                                    <p style="font-size:18px;">This Agreement sets forth the entire Agreement as to
                                        its subject matter. No modification, amendment, termination or waiver of this
                                        Agreement shall be binding unless in writing and signed by a duly authorized
                                        officer of <b>EMPLOYER</b>.  Failure of <b>EMPLOYER</b> to insist upon strict compliance with
                                        any of the terms, covenants or conditions of this Agreement shall not be deemed
                                        a waiver of such terms, covenants or conditions.</p>
                                </td>
                            </tr>
                            <tr>
                                <td style="width:2%;padding:4px;text-align:center;vertical-align:center;">

                                </td>
                                <td style="width:3%;padding:4px;text-align:center;vertical-align:center;">

                                </td>
                                <td style="width:3%;padding:4px;text-align:left;vertical-align:center;">
                                    <p style="font-size:18px;"><b>4.4</b></p>
                                </td>
                                <td style="width:92%;padding:4px;text-align:justify;vertical-align:center;">
                                    <p style="font-size:18px;">In the event of any dispute related to this Agreement,
                                        the prevailing party in that dispute shall recover its attorney fees.</p>
                                </td>
                            </tr>
                        </table>
                        <div class="text-justify">
                            <p style="font-size:18px;">D. This Agreement shall be effective on the date last written below.</p>
                        </div><br/>
                        <div class="row">
                            <div class="col-xs-5">
                                <div class="text-center">
                                    <b><t style="font-size:20px;text-align:center;" class="text-uppercase" t-esc="str(o.get_approvers_name(employee_id.id)).upper()"/></b>
                                    <span>_______________________________________</span><br/>
                                    <p style="font-size:18px;">Employee</p><br/><br/>
                                    <span>_______________________________________</span><br/>
                                    <p style="font-size:18px;">Signature of Employee</p><br/><br/><br/><br/><br/><br/><br/>
                                    <span>_______________________________________</span><br/>
                                    <p style="font-size:18px;">Date</p>
                                </div>

                            </div>
                            <div class="col-xs-1">
                                <span/>
                            </div>
                            <div class="col-xs-5">
                                <div class="text-center">
                                    <b><t style="font-size:20px;text-align:center;" class="text-uppercase" t-esc="company_id.name"/></b>
                                    <span>_______________________________________</span><br/>
                                    <p style="font-size:18px;">Employer</p><br/>
                                    <b><t style="font-size:20px;text-align:center;" class="text-uppercase" t-esc="str(o.get_approvers_name(signatory_id.id)).upper()"/></b>
                                    <span>_______________________________________</span><br/>
                                    <p style="font-size:18px;">Signature of Employer Representative</p><br/>
                                    <t class="text-uppercase" style="text-align:center;" t-esc="signatory_job_id"/>
                                    <span>_______________________________________</span><br/>
                                    <p style="font-size:18px;">Title</p><br/>
                                    <span>_______________________________________</span>
                                    <p style="font-size:18px;">Date</p>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                            <div class="col-xs-1">
                                <span/>
                            </div>
                        </div>
                    </div>
                </t>
            </t>
        </template>
    </data>
</odoo>